You will wake up tired the next morning
no matter how much you relax.
>> Really?
>> Yes. Because relaxation is only 50% of
the story. Our brain confuses physical
and mental exhaustion. It doesn't
distinguish well. So you are mentally
tired. Some people have very physically
demanding jobs. Most are sitting with a
screen all day. So when you get home,
you're not physically exhausted. You're
mentally drained.
>> Yes.
>> And then relaxing won't drain you
further, but it won't recharge you. It
won't fill the battery. What will fill
the battery is something active that is
recharging for you. If somebody's
creative, if they're a painter getting
up and painting for half an hour or
doing something creative, if they're an
organizer organizing, if they're
extrovert going and socializing and
forcing themselves to get up even though
they feel drained, they will come back
feeling more energized. They will sleep
better because relaxing is 50%,
recharging is 50%.